virtualdj.com 2018-12-31

# VIRTUAL DJ SOFTWARE - Disclaimer

**__  Virtual DJ Privacy Statement**

Atomix Productions

#### Privacy Policy

We, Atomix Productions, are the sole owner of the VirtualDJ website and VirtualDJ software (“VirtualDJ application”). We take our responsibility of protecting your personal information seriously and have created this Privacy Policy to help you understand the type of information we collect and your rights to and our responsibilities in safeguarding it.  
This Privacy Policy applies to any portion of the VirtualDJ website and software. It explains how we collect, use, under certain conditions, disclose your Personal Data and the steps we have taken to secure them.  
This Privacy Policy also explains your options regarding the collection, use and disclosure of your Personal Data.

#### Information Collection and Use

Atomix Productions collects information from our users at several different points on our website and software.  
We do not require any Personal Data to browse our Website or use our Software. All information gathered is on a voluntary basis. If you decide to provide us with your Personal Data, you should know that we may store all Personal Data that you provide to us through whatever means you provide such information (through our Website, Software, via email or phone, etc.). Examples of Personal Data include but are not limited to, your name, physical and/or email address, phone number, birthday, gender, location.  
Whatever the information we collect, as described below, we will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement.

#### Registration

In order to use some of the features in our software or on our website, the users have the opportunity to complete the registration form online from the VirtualDJ Website or in the VirtualDJ application. During registration a user is required to give his email, or sign in with a social media that will provide us with his email, and, optionally, other contact information. This information is used to contact the user about the services on our site for which they have expressed interest, and to allow a more intense involvement in the Virtual DJ community.

#### Order

We request information from the user on our Order Form, online from the VirtualDJ Website or in the VirtualDJ application, and will use the Personal Data disclosed on an Order Form to process and complete the customer's order, including shipping, calculation and processing of taxes or commissions and billing. Here a user must provide contact information (like name, email and shipping address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill customer’s orders.  
It is important to note that Atomix Productions DO NOT have access to the financial information that is gathered during an order. All orders are processed securely by third party companies specialized in payment processing. Atomix Productions never see your financial information nor do we store it in any of our databases.  
These third party companies are responsible for the use of the information they may gather.  
Please consult their privacy statements on their respective websites:

When a customer fills out and signs an order form, they consent to the collection, use and disclosure of their Personal Data for the purposes set out above, unless we are notified otherwise. VirtualDJ will only keep the Personal Data related to orders for lawful purposes.

#### Cookies

We may collect non-personally identifiable information automatically through the use of "cookies". A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s hard drive containing information about the user. Cookies do not contain any Personal Data, and usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. Once the user closes their browser, the cookie simply terminates. Cookies are optionally used on our website to the convenience of the user. You have the ability to set your browser to refuse cookies from websites or to remove cookies from your hard drive; if a user rejects the cookie, they may still use our site.  
We don't use to track and target the interests of our users, neither to transmit passwords.  
Some of our business partners use cookies on our site. However, we have no access to or control over these cookies.

#### Log Files

We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

#### Sharing

We will share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any Personal Data or personal information that can identify any individual person. We use an outside credit card processing company to bill users for goods and services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes.  
We partner with other parties to provide specific services, like music or video streaming. When the user signs up for these services, we will share names, or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services. These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services.

#### Outside European Union use

Your information may be processed and stored in the United States and the US government, courts or law enforcement agencies may be able to obtain disclosure of your information through lawful means in the US. We may also disclose personal data for detection and prevention of fraud. We reserve the right to transfer personal data in the event VirtualDJ acquires or merges with or is acquired by another company. Any information disclosed as a result of one of these events will be subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time.

#### Links

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we, Virtual DJ, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

#### Surveys & Contests

From time-to-time our site requests information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information, and demographic information. Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.

#### Security

VirtualDJ website and Application take every precaution to protect our users’ information. When users submit sensitive information, your information is protected both online and off-line.  
Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job are granted access to personally identifiable information. Our employees must use password-protected screen-savers when they leave their desk. When they return, they must re-enter their password to re-gain access to your information. Furthermore, ALL employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Every quarter, as well as any time new policies are added, our employees are notified and/or reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to ensure our customers’ information is protected.  
If you have any questions about the security at our website, you can contact us here.

#### Emails

We send emails to new members who register using an email address instead of a social media, in order to verify that the email address is correct.  
We also send emails as result of actions on our Website where the member specifically requested it, like password reset, or forum notifications.  
And, we occasionally send information on products, services, special deals, and newsletter, to members who opt-in to receive these emails. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications. Email preferences can be set on our Website on the User Profile section.

#### Correction/Updating Personal Information

If a user’s personally identifiable information changes, or if a user no longer desires our service, we will endeavor to provide a way to review, correct, update, withdraw or delete that user’s personal data provided to us. This can usually be done at the member information page or by emailing our Customer Support.

#### Notification of Changes

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our forum so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

#### Privacy Contact

For any further information about the privacy statement of Virtual DJ, please contact us here.
